<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/site/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/site/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-09T01:35:59+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/site/feed.xml</id><title type="html">MSc HCI - UPatras</title><subtitle>unoficial web site</subtitle><author><name>Department of Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering</name><email>hcimaster@upatras.gr</email><uri>https://hcimaster.upatras.gr</uri></author><entry><title type="html">Call for applications 2020-2021</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/11/23/call-for-2020-2021/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Call for applications 2020-2021" /><published>2019-11-23T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-11-23T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/11/23/call-for-2020-2021</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/11/23/call-for-2020-2021/">&lt;p&gt;Expression of interest for admission of new students for the course starting in October 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eligibility criteria&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidates should hold an undergraduate degree in the fields of Computer Engineering, Informatics, Electronic/Electrical Engineering, Physics, Mathematics or similar science fields, from recognised institutions in Greece or abroad. Applications may also be submitted by graduates of departments/faculties who have not completed their studies before the application deadline, who however are expected to graduate before the beginning of the program. These candidates may be conditionally accepted. These candidates, if successfully evaluated, will be requested to submit a Certificate of Completion of their studies by November 1st at the latest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The selection criteria include: a graduation grade of at least 7/10 or equivalent, taking into account the graduation classification (Excellent, Very Good). The transcript of academic records should include subjects of at least 20 ECTS or equivalent in the area of computing. English language competence that can be proved by a certificate of linguistic skills at least of level B2 or equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Submission process – timeline&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phase 1. Prepare necessary documents and submit application through the application form by the 25st of July 2019. The supporting documents for Applications for Entry in the Master Program are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae
Copies of Degree Certificates
Transcript of Academic Records
Motivation Letter of maximum 2 pages including the research interests of the candidate
Proof of English language competence (level B2 or higher) plus additional foreign language skills
Two Recommendation letters (details of recommenders)
Copies of Scientific Publications relevant to the topic of the Master Program (if available)
Photocopy of Identity Card or Passport
Photo (ID Card type)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phase 2. The selection committee will invite candidates who meet the eligibility requirements for an interview (skype or in person) during the first week of September 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phase 3. Decision on selection of candidates. On September, the decision of the selection committee will be announced. The candidates who have been selected, will be called to register with the University of Patras through its electronic registry by September 30th, 2020. The courses start on October the 1st.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Department of Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering</name><email>hcimaster@upatras.gr</email><uri>https://hcimaster.upatras.gr</uri></author><category term="[&quot;secretary&quot;, &quot;students&quot;]" /><category term="admission" /><category term="application" /><summary type="html">Expression of interest for admission of new students for the course starting in October 2020</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ieeevr</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/10/14/IEEEVR/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ieeevr" /><published>2019-10-14T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-14T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/10/14/IEEEVR</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/10/14/IEEEVR/">&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;title: “IEEE VR Contest”
excerpt: “Expression of interest for IEEE VR Contest”
category:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;students
tags:&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IEEE VR&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h2 id=&quot;contest&quot;&gt;Contest&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Αγαπητοί φοιτητές,&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Την ερχόμενη Παρασκευή 18/10, στις 11 το πρωί, στο χώρο που κάνουμε εργαστήριο, 
θα οριστούν οι ομάδες που θα συμεμτάσχουν στο διαγωνισμό του ΙΕΕΕ VR.
Παρακαλώ όσες ομάδες φοιτητών, αλλά και μεμονωμένα άτομα, ενδιαφέρονται να έρθουν για συζήτηση
μαζί με θεματικές προτάσεις επί του προβλήματος του διαγωνισμού για να οριστικοποιήσουμε τις συμμετοχές.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ΚΜ&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Department of Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering</name><email>hcimaster@upatras.gr</email><uri>https://hcimaster.upatras.gr</uri></author><summary type="html">title: “IEEE VR Contest” excerpt: “Expression of interest for IEEE VR Contest” category: students tags: IEEE VR Contest Αγαπητοί φοιτητές,</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">HCI Master Orientation Event</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/10/03/HCIMasterOrientationEvent/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="HCI Master Orientation Event" /><published>2019-10-03T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-03T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/10/03/HCIMasterOrientationEvent</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/site/posts/2019/10/03/HCIMasterOrientationEvent/">&lt;p&gt;On October 3rd the Introductory and Orientation event of the HCI Master for academic year 2019-2020 took place. 
The event was opened by a welcome message of Prof. Stavros Koubias, Head of the Electrical and Computer Engineering Department and a 
welcome address by Prof. Stratis Gallopoulos, Head of the Computer Engineering and Informatics Department. 
They both made reference to the importane of the new Program for the area of computer science and technology. T
Then an introduction to the program objectives and structure was made by the coordinators Profs N. Avouris and M. Xenos, followed by 
more detailed presentation of the program of study by faculty members. The new students then presented themselves and their particular
aspirations with respect to the new program.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Department of Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering</name><email>hcimaster@upatras.gr</email><uri>https://hcimaster.upatras.gr</uri></author><category term="[&quot;secretary&quot;, &quot;students&quot;]" /><category term="orientation event" /><summary type="html">Event of October 3rd, Introductory and Orientation event of the HCI Master for academic year 2019-2020</summary></entry></feed>